<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/white"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="PRIVACY POLICY \n\nA privacy policy is a statement or a legal document (in privacy law) that discloses some or all of the ways a party gathers, uses, discloses, and manages a customer or client's data. It fulfills a legal requirement to protect a customer or client's privacy. \n\nOVERVIEW \n\nEarnReal is committed to safeguard the privacy of our users personal data; in this policy we explain how your personal data and any information relating to you, that we may hold about you, is collected, used, stored, disclosed, and removed (each and all referred to as processing). This Policy only applies to information we process. It does not apply to the practices of companies that we don't own or control, or employees that we don't manage. Information on our services’ may contain links to third party sites, and any information you provide to those sites will be covered by any privacy policies they may have. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is those sites' responsibility to protect any information you give them, so we can't be held liable for their wrongful use of your personally identifying information. We may update this policy from time to time. \n\nUSER DATA \n\nWe may process your registration data (registration data). Registration data may include your name, email address and password. The source of the registration data is you. Registration data is required in order to make you able to use the service. We may process your account data (account data). Account data may include your full name, email address, country and phone number. The source of the account data is you. \nThe account data may be processed for the purposes of providing our services, ensuring the security of our users and services, and communicating with you. We may collect and process your identity documents (ID data). Verifying account with ID which may contain your full name, country, date of birth, country national id number and gender. The purpose for ID data is to protect our users from fraud and helps us to prevent, detect and investigate fraud, money laundering, criminal activity or other misuse of our service. ID creates a strong assumption about the ownership of the account and thus ensures that we can return access to your account in case your account is hacked. Legal bases for this processing are consent and legitimate interests of ours and/or by third-parties, namely to prevent, detect and investigate fraud, criminal activity or other misuse of the services and to prevent security issues. We may process data about your use of our app and services (usage data). Usage data is primarily non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers, servers, and services like Google Analytics typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the time of each visit. Other non-identifying information that we might have access to include how you use the service (e.g. search queries), your approximate location, and cookies set by our app, etc. Usage data may include: 1) Data that we collect mainly for behavior statistics, business intelligence and email campaigns (analytics data).We gather event based tracking data with the help of Mix panel, and this data may also contain your email address, IP address and country code. 2) Data that we collect mainly for technical, security and/or fraud prevention reasons or for tracking errors. We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or what you generate through the use of our service (communication data). Communication data includes 1) all your messages, requests and other communication with our customer support which may happen during the dispute review process or via support tickets, emails, or by means of any other communication tool. Communication data may include, email address, username, IP address, full name, audio and video files and in the case of manual ID verification: photo of the user’s personal ID, photo of the user, and photo of the user’s utility bill or related document. The communication data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you, record-keeping, in order to review and resolve disputes, serve our customers better and improve our service. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our business. We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications, SMS notifications and/or newsletters (notification data). The notification data may include your email address, phone number and full name. The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent. You can unsubscribe at any point by contacting us or by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email. We may process any of your personal data when necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or outside the court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.\n\nUSER RIGHTS \n\nWe have summarized the principal rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, might contain restrictions depending on the legal basis for processing the data and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal. You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by contacting our customer support. Concerning Right to erasure users are also able to request the deletion of their account by contacting us."
        android:layout_margin="20dp"
        android:paddingBottom="40dp"
        android:textColor="@color/black"
        android:textSize="15sp" />


</ScrollView>